ILR School Associate Dean's Office Files /4217
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Annual Reports and Summaries of Progress, 1946-1960. (Box 15)
  - Report of the Dean, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Summary: Extension Division Programs, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    July 1 1950-June 30 1960
  - Report of the Dean New York State School of Industrial and Labor relations, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Summary, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    July 1,1958- June 30, 1959
  - Extension Program Summary, 1958-1959 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Summary Extension Divisions Programs, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    July 1,1957- June 30, 1958
  - Extension Program Summary, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    July 1,1955- June 30, 1956
  - Summary of Extension Division Programs, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    July 1, 1956- June 30,1957
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    July 1, 1955- June 30, 1956
  - Extension Summary, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    July 1 1954- June 30, 1955
  - Summary, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    July 1, 1953- June 30, 1954
  - Summary, 1953-1954 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    July 1, 1952- June 30, 1953
  - Summary, 1952-1953 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Only Copy- Do not Remove From File
  - Summary, 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    Only Copy Do not remove from file
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    July 1,1950- June 30, 1951
  - Summary, 1950-1951 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Only copy do not remove from file
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    July1, 1949- June 30, 1950
  - Summary, 1949-1950 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    July 1, 1948- June 30, 1949
  - Summary, 1948-1949 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Only Copy- Do Not Remove From File
  - Summary, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Summary, 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Annual Report For Extension Division, 1946-1947 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Annual Reports and Summaries of Progress, 1960-1987. (Box 16)
  - Report of the Dean of New York State School Industrial Labor and Relations, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Annual Summary Extension Division, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Summary of Extension division Programs, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    July 1, 1960- June 30, 1961
  - Annual Summary extension Division, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Report of the Dean, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Report of the dean New York State School Industrial and Labor Relations, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs July 1,1962- June 30, 1963, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    July 1,1962- June 30, 1963
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    July 1,1963- June 30, 1964
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    July 1,1964- June 30, 1965
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    April 1, 1965- March 31, 1966
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    April 1, 1966- March 31, 1967
  - Summary Extension Division Programs July 1,1962- June 30, 1963, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    April 1, 1967- March 31, 1968
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    April 1, 1968- March 31, 1969
  - Summary of Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    April 1, 1969- March 31, 1970
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    April 1, 1970- March 31, 1971
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    April 1, 1971- March 31, 1972
  - Summary Extension Division Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Extension Summary of Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    April 1, 1972- March 31, 1973
  - Extension of programs announcements, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    April 1, 1973- March 31, 1974
  - Annual Summary of Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - New York State School Industrial and Labor Relations Extension Annual Reports 1976-1987 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Personnel Files, 1971-1983. (Box 17)
  - Brooks, George, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Brophy, Jacqueline, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Charles Crapo, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Dennis, Rodney, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - R Dennis, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Memos to Rod Dennis, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Doherty, Robert, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Donovan Ronald, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - William Fowler, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Frank, William, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Julian Robert, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Matt Kelly, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Hqmer LaRUE, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Levine, Stephen H., 1981 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Joseph Musicus, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Donno Nerboso, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Roberts, Seth, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Duane Wilcox, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- New York State AFL-CIO Research Files, 1956-1992. (Box 18)
  - New York State School AFL CIO Raymond R. Corbett, 1963-1981, 1992 Remarks Statements obituary (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - New York State School AFL CIO: Harold C.Hanover, 1958-1962 Speeches remarks Press releases (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Louis Hollander, 1956-1963 Speeches Memoranda press releases biographical notes (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Ludwig Jaffe, 1959 Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - George Meany, 1980 Press releases, Memorial Statements (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - History of the New York State School AFL CIO: Untitled undated draft pp 14-48-57-96 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - History of the New York State School AFL CIO: Untitled undated draft23 pages (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - History of the New York State School AFL CIO from 1864 to 1958 Leslie Braginsky 1988 pp 1-20 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - A tradition of leadership: A History of the New York State School AFL CIO draft 1, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - A tradition of Leadership, 1865-1990 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - AFL CIO:Merger 1956-1959 Agreements Resolutions, Memoranda articles, reports (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Child Labor, 1960-1976 Articles, Memoranda, Press releases (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Discrimination 1977-1980 Remarks, Memoranda (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Economic Development of New York State School 1977-1982 statements and press releases (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Education, 1960-1971 Speeches, Statements, Memoranda (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Farm Workers 1967-1971 speeches, memoranda (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Immigration, 1975-1976 Statements, Memoranda (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Juvenile delinquency, 1958 Resolutions, articles (Box 18, Folder 18)
- New York State AFL-CIO Research Files, 1955-1983. (Box 19)
  - Labor Legislation, 1959, Articles Press Releases (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Minimum Wage, 1975 Statements (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - New York State Federation of Labor, 1919 Report (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Occupational Safety and Health, 1973-1980 Statements speeches (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Platform proposals presented to the republican State Platform Committee, 1978 press release (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Labor proposals to the 1976 national democratic Party Platform statement (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Power resources, 1955 statements (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Public employees 1966-1970, 1982 Memoranda press releases (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Sexual Discrimination, 1973-1979 Statements, press releases, memoranda articles (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Workmen's compensation, 1959 Memoranda (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - General, 1957-1963, 1981-1983, press releases, Memoranda, articles (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Annual Reports 1992-1996; 1999-2001. Faculty obituaries. (Box 20)
  - Annual Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Jean Mckelvey 1 of 3, 1908-1998 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Jean Mckelvey, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Jean Mckelvey 2 of 3, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Alice B Grant, 1922-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Jennie Farley Memorial Bio, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Matt Kelly, 1913-1993 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Memorial Bios (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Abraham AL Nash, 1915-1996 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Mayer Wertheimer Died September 20th 1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Alice Hanson Cook, 1903-1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - William F. Whyte Memorial (Box 20, Folder 13)